Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Werther, William B. - Zwerdling, Daniel., Publication (Box 27)
  - Zinober, Peter W. Esq. & Locklear, Melanie N. "The Use of Expert Witnesses and Specialists in Employment Cases", Publication (Box 27, Folder 118)
    - Item 1: The Use of Expert Witnesses and Specialists in Employment Cases, 1992; Publication (Box 27, Folder 118)
      Author: Peter W. Zinober Esq. and Melanie N. Locklear
  - Ziskin, Ian V., "Knowledge Based Pay: A Strategic Analysis", Publication (Box 27, Folder 119)
    - Item 1: Knowledge-Based Pay: A Strategic Analysis, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 119)
      Author: Ian V. Ziskin
  - Zuboff, Shoshanna, "New Worlds of Computer-Mediated Work", Publication (Box 27, Folder 120)
    - Item 1: New Worlds of Computer-Mediated Work, 1982; Publication (Box 27, Folder 120)
      Author: Shoshana Zuboff
  - Zwerdling, Daniel, An Overview of Alternative Approaches to Worker Participation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 121)
    - Item 1: An Overview of Alternative Approaches to Worker Participation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 121)
      Author: Daniel Zwerdling
  - Zwerdling, Daniel, "Employee Ownership: How Well is it Working?", Publication (Box 27, Folder 122)
    - Item 1: Employee Ownership: How Well Is It Working?, 1979; Publication (Box 27, Folder 122)